Abrar Dewa Pratama Barus

Medan | +62 812 6582 2784 | abrarpratama5228@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a fresh graduate of informatics engineering at Sumatera Institute of Technology. I have an interest in web developer especially in frontend and I have an experience and passion for responsive design using Bootstrap, Ant Design and Tailwind CSS. I have experience working with teams to produce impactful.

EXPERIENCE

PT. Bank OCBC NISP- Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Engineer (August 2022 - Current)

- Collaborated and develop feature and maintenance web using react js, typescript, HTML, CSS and Ant Design.
- Use Agile methodologies (Scrum) to collaborated with stakeholders during development processes and use Jira as a support tools.

PT. IMPACT BYTE TEKNOLOGI EDUKASI (SKILVUL) - Jakarta, Indonesia

UI/UX Designer (August 2021 - December 2021)

- Used wireframes, mock-ups and prototypes to establish user interface design and architecture.
- Conducted live user testing of components and functionality to evaluate effectiveness of designs and enhancements.

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA – Lampung, Indonesia

Frontend Developer (May 2021 - August 2021)

- Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Coded using JavaScript and CSS using React Native and Bootstrap to develop features for mobile platforms.

EDUCATION

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA (2018-2022)

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering - GPA 3.3

SKILLS

- Web and Mobile frontend development
- Organization and Time Management
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP
- ANT Design, Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS